*** Informations for compatibility
	9 0
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	IN 		#Input pin of type DT.
	BYTE1 		#First (lowest) BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE2 		#Second BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE3 		#Third BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE4 		#Fourth BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE5 		#Fifth BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE6 		#Sixth BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE7 		#Seventh BYTE of the input DT.
	BYTE8 		#Eight (hightes) BYTE of the input DT.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converts a DT into eight BYTEs.
Use to convert a DT into eight BYTEs. The lowest part of the DT is the output pin BYTE1 and the highest part is pin BYTE8.
