*** Informations for compatibility
	3 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	LOW 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the lower part of the DWORD.
	HIGH 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the higher part of the DWORD.
	OUT 		#Output of type DWORD consiting of the two input WORDs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst two WORDs to a DWORD.
Use to convert two WORDs to a value of type DWORD. Input pin LOW becomes the lower part of the DWORD value and pin HIGH becomes the higher part of the DWORD value.
