*** Informations for compatibility
	5 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	W1 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 1 (lowest) part of the DT.
	W2 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 2 part of the DT.
	W3 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 3 part of the DT.
	W4 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 4 (highest) part of the DT.
	OUT 		#Output of type DT consiting of the four input WORDs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst four WORDs to a DT.
Use to convert four WORDs to a value of type DT. Input pin W1 becomes the lowest part of the DT value and pin W4 becomes the highest part of the DT value.
