*** Informations for compatibility
	9 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	W1 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 1 (lowest) part of the STRING.
	W2 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 2 part of the STRING.
	W3 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 3 part of the STRING.
	W4 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 4 part of the STRING.
	W5 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 5 part of the STRING.
	W6 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 6 part of the STRING.
	W7 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 7 part of the STRING.
	W8 		#Input pin of type WORD which becomes the 8 (hightes) part of the STRING.
	OUT 		#Output of type STRING consiting of the eight input WORDs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst eight WORDs to a STRING.
Use to convert eight WORDs to a value of type STRING. Input pin W1 becomes the lowest part of the STRING value and pin W8 becomes the highest part of the STRING value.
