*** Informations for compatibility
	9 0
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	IN 		#Input pin of type STRING.
	W1 		#First (lowest) WORD of the input STRING.
	W2 		#Second WORD of the input STRING.
	W3 		#Third WORD of the input STRING.
	W4 		#Fourth WORD of the input STRING.
	W5 		#Fifth WORD of the input STRING.
	W6 		#Sixth WORD of the input STRING.
	W7 		#Seventh WORD of the input STRING.
	W8 		#Eight (hightes) WORD of the input STRING.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converts a STRING into two WORDs.
Use to convert a STRING into two WORDs. The lowest part of the STRING is the output pin W1 and the highest part is pin W8.
