*** Informations for compatibility
	9 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	BYTE1 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 1 (lowest) part of the DT.
	BYTE2 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 2 part of the DT.
	BYTE3 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 3 part of the DT.
	BYTE4 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 4 part of the DT.
	BYTE5 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 5 part of the DT.
	BYTE6 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 6 part of the DT.
	BYTE7 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 7 part of the DT.
	BYTE8 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 8 (hightes) part of the DT.
	OUT 		#Output of type DT consiting of the eight input BYTEs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst eight BYTEs to a DT.
Use to convert eight BYTEs to a value of type DT. Input pin BYTE1 becomes the lowest part of the DT value and pin BYTE8 becomes the highest part of the DT value.
