*** Informations for compatibility
	5 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	BYTE1 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 1st (lowest) part of the DWORD.
	BYTE2 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 2nd part of the DWORD.
	BYTE3 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 3rd part of the DWORD.
	BYTE4 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the 4nd part of the DWORD.
	OUT 		#Output of type DINT consisting of the four input BYTEs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst four BYTEs to a DINT.
Use to convert four BYTEs to a value of type DINT. Input pin BYTE1 becomes the lowest part of the DINT value and pin BYTE4 becomes the highest part of the DINT value.
