*** Informations for compatibility
	2 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	BYTE1 		#Input pin of type BYTE which becomes the higher part of the UINT.
	OUT 		#Output of type TOD consisting of the four input BYTEs.
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Converst two BYTEs to a UINT.
Use to convert two BYTEs to a value of type UINT. Input pin BYTE1 becomes the lower part of the INT value and pin BYTE2 becomes the higher part of the INT value.
