*** Informations for compatibility
	3 1
*** List param and result : <Name:8 characters max, not translatable> [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	IN1 		#Wert, von dem die Exponentialfunktion per Exponent ermittelt werden soll
	IN2 		#Exponent der Exponentialfunktion 
	OUTP 		#Natürliche Exponentialfunktion von IN1
*** EF/EFB comment : "MAIN_COMMENT" [#<Comment:1024 characters max, translatable>]
	MAIN_COMMENT 		#Exponentiation eines Wertes durch einen anderen Wert 
This is the descriptive form of the demonstration EF
